Population Council records, Board of Trustees Meetings, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 9 FA1429
Rockefeller Archive Center
Population Council records, Board of Trustees Meetings, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 9
1952-1989
Rockefeller Archive Center
Population Council
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison) (1906-1978)
FA1429
14.43 Cubic Feet 38 letter document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Primarily arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
Meetings of the Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, Annual Meeting of the Members, and select Officer's meetings. Files often contain dockets, agendas, minutes, financial reports, and associated background information for each meeting.
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1952 November 17-1954 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1955 January 24-1956 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1955 January 24-1956 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1957 January 10-1958 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1957 January 10-1958 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1958 November 13-1960 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1959 January 21-May 13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1960 January 6-October 19 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1960 April 5-October 19 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1961 January 11-December 20 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1962 March 14-October 10 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1963 January 7-April 17 (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1963 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1973 February (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1964 May 20-October 14 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1965 January 13-April 21 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1965 October 20-December 15 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1966 April 20-October 19 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1966 December 21-1967 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1967 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1967 October 11 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1967 October 11-December 13 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1967 December 13 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Annual Meeting and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1968 April 2 (Box 7, Folder 30-31)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1968 October 16 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1968 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 March 5 (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 June 4 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 June 4 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1969 September 17 (Box 9, Folder 40-41)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 December 10 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1970 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1970 June 3 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 September 9 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1970 December 9 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1971 March 3 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1971 June 2 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1971 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1971 December 7 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 March 8 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 September 13 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 December 13 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 March 7 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1973 June 6 (Box 36, Folder 118)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 September 5 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1973 December 12 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 March 6 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1974 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 September 11 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1974 October 7; December 3 1974 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 March 25 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1975 June 4 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 September 8 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1975 December 10 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Board of Trustees Meeting (George Zeidenstein Copy), 1976 April 5 (Box 13, Folder 66-67)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting (George Zeidenstein Copy), 1976 June 8-9 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Executive Committee Meeting (George Zeidenstein Copy), 1976 September 8 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Board of Trustees Meeting (George Zeidenstein Copy), 1976 December 7-8 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Executive Committee Meeting (George Zeidenstein Copy), 1977 March 2 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 June 14-15 (Box 14, Folder 72-73)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1978 April 21 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1978 June 23-24 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Executive Committee, 1978 September 15 (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 78)
- Senior Staff Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 119)
- Family Planning Programs and Official Policy Decisions in Southern Africa, John C. Caldwell, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 120)
- Officers Meetings, 1976 July-1977 March (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Officers Meetings, 1977 April-November (Box 16, Folder 80)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1976 June 8-9 (Box 16, Folder 81)
- Executive Committee Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1976 September 8 (Box 16, Folder 82)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 December 7-8 (Box 16, Folder 83)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1977 March 2 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 June 4-5 (Box 16, Folder 85)
- Executive Committee Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1977 September 8 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 December 6-7 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Executive Committee Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1978 April 21 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1978 June 23-24 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1978 September 15 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1978 December 1-2 (Box 17, Folder 91)
- 1979 Program Budget, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 121)
- Officers Meetings, 1979 January-February (Box 18, Folder 92)
- Officers Meetings, 1979 March-June (Box 18, Folder 93)
- Officers Meetings, 1979 July-December (Box 18, Folder 94)
- Officers Meetings, 1979 January-December (Box 18, Folder 95)
- 1980 Program Plan and Budget, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 122)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1979 June 15-16 (Box 18, Folder 96)
- Executive Committee Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1979 March 2 (Box 19, Folder 97)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 September 14 (Box 19, Folder 98)
- Board of Trustees Meeting (Hugo Hoogenboom Copy), 1979 December 7-8 (Box 19, Folder 99)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 June 12-14 (Box 19, Folder 100)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 September 23 (Box 19, Folder 101)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 December 5-6 (Box 19, Folder 102)
- Officers Meetings, 1980 January-February (Box 19, Folder 103)
- Officers Meetings, 1980 March-May (Box 20, Folder 104)
- Officers Meetings, 1980 June-September (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Officers Meetings, 1980 October-December (Box 20, Folder 106)
- Officers Meetings, 1980 January-December (Box 20, Folder 107)
- Officers Meetings, 1981 January-July (Box 20, Folder 108)
- Officers Meetings, 1981 August-December (Box 21, Folder 109)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1981 March 24 (Box 21, Folder 110)
- Annual Meeting of Members and Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 June 5-6 (Box 21, Folder 111)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1981 September 22 (Box 21, Folder 112)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 December 4-5 (Box 21, Folder 113)
- Officers Meetings, 1982 January-December (Box 37, Folder 131)
- Officers Meetings, 1983 January-June (Box 21, Folder 114)
- Officers Meetings, 1983 July-December (Box 21, Folder 115)
- Officers Meetings, 1984 January-June (Box 22, Folder 116)
- Officers Meetings, 1984 July-December (Box 22, Folder 117)
- Board of Trustees - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 123)
- Board of Trustees - Members - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 124)
- Board of Trustees - Members - Black, Eugene, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 125)
- Board of Trustees - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 126)
- Board of Trustees - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Travel - Taiwan, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 127)
- Board of Trustees - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Travel - Philippines and Japan, 1970-1972 (Box 37, Folder 128)
- Executive Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 129)
- Annual Meeting, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 130)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 131-132)
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 133)
  Scope and Contents
  Also includes Annual Meeting
- Board of Trustees Meetings, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 134)
- Executive Committee Meetings, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 135)
- Executive Committee Meetings, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 136-137)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1952 November 17-1961 December 20; 2 Volumes (Box 22)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Brittle or damaged items may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1962 May 23-1969 June 4; 2 Volumes (Box 23)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1970 March 4-1976 June 8-9; 2 Volumes (Box 24)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1976 September-December; 2 Volumes (Box 25)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1977 March; June; September; 2 Volumes (Box 26)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1977 December-1978 September; 2 Volumes (Box 27)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1978 December-1979 December; 2 Volumes (Box 28)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1979 December-1980 September; 2 Volumes (Box 29)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1980 December-1981 March; 2 Volumes (Box 30)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1981 December-1982 December; 2 Volumes (Box 31)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1983-1984 June; 2 Volumes (Box 32)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1984 December-1985 September; 2 Volumes (Box 33)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1985 December-1986 December; 2 Volumes (Box 34)
- Board of Trustees Meetings - Bound Volumes, 1987 December-1989 December; 2 Volumes (Box 35)